(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)＜バンとキング
死者の都に向かった二人が➡
Band and King faced off in the Capital of the Dead, chasing after the same person:
追っていたのは キングの妹
妖精のエレインであった＞
King's sister, the fairy Elaine.
＜キングは
エレインを殺された憎しみから➡
King held a grudge against Ban for killing Elaine, so he turned him into stone.
バンを石化するが
それを救ったのは➡
However, none other than
Elaine appeared to save Ban.
ほかならぬ エレインであった＞
And the story of Elaine and Ban's past was revealed.
＜ そして 明らかになる
バンとエレインの過去＞
＜エレインが死に至った真相＞
And the truth behind Elaine's death.
ザシュ！
But then they were attacked by the Holy Knight Guila.
＜ そこに襲いかかる
聖騎士ギーラ＞
＜死んだ者しか入れない
といわれる死者の都で➡
Now, within the Capital of the Dead,
where only the nonliving dwell, the battle rages on.
戦いは続いていた＞
ドスッ！
んおっ？ 何？
ん？
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)やあ バン｡
Hey, Ban.
げほっ！
おいおい なんのまねだ？ キング｡
Hey now, King. What's the deal?
見れば分かるだろ｡
助けに来たのさ｡
Isn't it obvious? I came to save you.
Save me, eh? Much appreciated.
助けにねぇ｡ そりゃどうも｡
You're most welcome.
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)どういたしまして｡
団長とディアンヌのためだもの｡
I'm doing this for Captain and Diane.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)あらら～ 俺は なしかよ？
Oh? You're leaving me out?
And there's also...
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)そうだね｡ あとは➡
Elaine's feelings for you.
君を思う妹のためさ｡
(ｴﾚｲﾝ･心の声)
≪お願い… 必ず バンを守って≫
Please...
Protect Ban.
＜ これは いまだ
人と 人ならざるものの世界が➡
This is a tale of humans and beings from other worlds.
分かたれてはいなかった
古の物語＞
It is a story of ancient times.
＜聖騎士は かつて
他の三つの種族と共に➡
Long ago, the Holy Knights fought alongside three tribes to seal away the Demon Clan.
魔神族を闇に葬った＞
It was known as the Holy War, and memory of it has long left the minds of the people.
＜聖戦と呼ばれたその戦いは➡
時を経て 人々の記憶から
消えてなくなった＞
＜ だが 今再び 聖戦が叫ばれる＞
However, a new Holy War has begun.
＜七つの大罪を葬り去れと＞
The battle to banish the Seven Deadly Sins unto oblivion.
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
I continue to take everything in my arms
subete o daite koko ni irun da
For that's where our light lies
hikari wa soko ni aru yo
With unyielding emotions in tow,
yuzurenai omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me to you
yume o tsunaida kimi to
A beginning will someday be born from our own hands
hajimari o itsuka bokura no te de umidasun da yo
And with how kind you are, I'm sure your voice will be able to change the world
yasashii kimi no koe mo kitto sekai o kaerareru
Since people can't totally stand up all on their own,
dare mo hitori kiri ja tachiagare yashinai kara
we'll reach out our hands to one another
tagai ni te o nobashite
and head for a tomorrow that surpasses all limits
kagiri no koeta ashita e
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
As we begin to butt heads and get to know one another better,
butsukariatte wakariaun da
we'll create a path of light.
hikari o tsukuridasu yo
Guided by my tenacity,
akiramenu omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me with you
yume o tsunai da kimi to
Episode 9
Dark Pulse
ドォーン！
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ほう～｡
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)あなたの裏切りは
想定内ではありました｡
I always figured you'd betray me.
が やはり残念です｡
怠惰の罪のキング｡
But it's still a shame, Grizzly's Sin of Sloth, King.
その発言は想定外だね｡
You really call this a betrayal?
おいらは はなから 王国聖騎士の
仲間になったつもりはないよ｡➡
I had no intention of siding with you from the start.
It just so happened that the Kingdom's goal of defeating the Seven Deadly Sins
七つの大罪を倒したい王国側と
バンを倒したいおいらとで➡
coincided with my goal of defeating Ban.
一瞬 目的が一致しただけ｡
でも 事情が変わってさ｡
But the situation's changed.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)
どうでもいいけど さっきから➡
I really couldn't care less, but would you stop literally talking about me behind my back?
人の背中越しにしゃべんな｡
I see. That's quite the assumption you have there.
なるほど 想定内の言い訳ですね｡
ショットボム！
Short Bomb!
Short Bomb
ふん｡
ぐはっ｡
ドォーーン！
(ﾎｰｸ)うおいっ！
Whoa!
なんか すごいことになってるぜ！
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ)急ぎましょう！
Looks like something big is going on over there!
Let's hurry!
Let's turn back!
やっぱり 引き返そうぜ…｡
ダメ！
We can't!
Amazing...
すばらしい｡➡
それが 妖精界に存在する
神樹から作られたといわれる➡
So that's the legendary Spirit Spear, Chastiefol, a holy weapon crafted from the Sacred Tree
found only in the Fairy Realm.
霊槍シャスティフォル｡➡
They say it's stronger than steel, and that it holds the mysterious qualities of the Sacred Tree.
強度は 鋼をも上回り➡
神樹の不思議な特性を
併せ持つとか｡
あなたの魔力は
その特性を 全て引き出す➡
And your power to evoke those qualities is...
｢災厄｣｡
"Disaster."
Disaster
これで 少しは楽しめそうです｡
Seems like this might be fun after all.
よろしければ ４対１でどうぞ｡
Please, come at me four-on-one.
いや １対１だ｡
No, it'll be one-on-one.
Is that a joke?
正気ですか？
(ﾒﾘｵﾀﾞｽ)頼んだぞ キング！
負けたら ぶっ殺す｡
We're counting on you, King!
If you lose, I'll kill you!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)ねえ 団長…
僕 もうダメかもぉ…｡
Captain... I think... I might be... dying...
ふっ いいでしょう｡
さあ いつでも…｡
As you wish.
Well, whenever you're rea—
That's no good. You should at least try to dodge.
ダメじゃないか
ちゃんとよけなきゃ｡
I misread it?!
≪読み違えた!?≫
This speed...
≪この速度 この威力！
ほかの七つの大罪とは…≫
This power...
Compared to the other Sins...
≪私は知っている≫
I already know...
≪あなたは
願いをかなえてくれることを｡➡
that you'll grant my wish.
あなたは 自分のためよりも➡
Your power is stronger when you wield it for others.
誰かのために
力を発揮できるから≫
Not just for me,
(ｴﾚｲﾝ)≪妹のためだけでなく➡
but for your friends who need you.
あなたを求める
仲間たちのため≫
(ｴﾚｲﾝ)≪私は知っている｡➡
I know...
that you're kinder than anyone else.
あなたが 誰より優しいことを｡➡
焼き尽くされた故郷の前で➡
After you saw that your
hometown had burned down,
自分を責め 私と民のために
涙を流し続けたことを≫
I know how you kept blaming yourself and
shed countless tears for me and your people...
くっ！
ドォーン！
(ｴﾚｲﾝ)≪私は知っている｡➡
I know...
that your power can be immeasurable.
あなたの
計り知れない その魔力を≫
Brilliant Detonation!
ブリリアント･デトネーション！
Brilliant Detonation
Whoa now.
(ｴﾚｲﾝ)≪かつて 人間の王国は➡
In the past, the Human Kingdom was at peace with the Fairy King's Forest.
妖精王の治める森と
和平を結んでいた｡➡
それは 必ずしも
友好の証しだけではなく➡
Not only was it a sign of friendship,
互いに干渉し合わないようにとの
密約でもあった≫
it was also an agreement not to
interfere with each other's kingdoms.
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)
霊槍シャスティフォル 第五形態➡
Spirit Spear Chastiefol, Form Five.
Increase!
Increase
｢増殖｣！
パチン
(ｴﾚｲﾝ)
≪でも 人が何より恐れたのは➡
But what commanded the most respect...
何人の侵入も拒み 恐怖を与えた➡
What repelled every invasion and struck fear into those who tried...
was the power of the Fairy King.
妖精王の魔力≫
≪｢キング｣｡ 誠の名を…≫
King...
His true name...
(ｴﾚｲﾝ)≪妖精王 ハーレクイン≫
Fairy King, Harlequin.
パカパカ パカパカ…(足音)
お～い！
Hey!
That's quite a mess you've made!
こりゃまた 派手にやったな｡
おケガはありませんか!?
Is anyone hurt?
Hey! We're all fine!
おう！ みんな 無事 無事｡
Thank goodness.
よかった｡
ふっ｡
この至近距離では！
なっ！
At this range,
霊槍の防御をもってしても
タダでは済まない！
not even defending with the Spirit Spear will save you!
キン！
お前がな｡
Worry about saving yourself.
Damn!
しまった！ ｢全反撃｣…｡
Full Counter!
ドォーーン！
メリオダス様…｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)ギーラの気配が消えた｡
Lord Meliodas...
Guila's presence disappeared.
おそらく 今の衝撃で
元の世界に戻ったのね｡
That impact probably sent her back to the real world.
生身でやってきた
あなたたちと違って➡
Unlike you all, it seems she came here with just her soul instead of her physical body.
魂だけのようだったから｡
プゴォ～！ お… 俺の耳が ねぇ！
M-My ears are gone!
Hawk!
ホークちゃん！
えっ？ あっ 私も…｡
It's happening to me too! What's going on?!
なんです これ!? 気持ち悪～い！
I don't like this feeling!
よし！ じゃあ 気持ちよくするか｡
Here! I'll make you feel better!
ああ～！
何してんの 団長！ って 何これ!?
Hey! What do you think you're doing, Captain?!
What's going on?!
It appears this world has begun to reject you,
since the living do not belong here.
(ﾙｲｼﾞ)死者の都が
本来 ここにいるべきではない➡
おにいちゃんたちを
拒絶しはじめたんだよ｡➡
It's great that you found
who you were searching for.
よかったね 会いたい人に会えて｡
Why are you guys here?
お前ら なんでここに…｡
まさか
もともと こっちの世界の住人｡
Don't tell me, you guys are from this world?
(ｴﾚﾝ)
料理 とっても おいしかったよ｡
Your cooking was really delicious. Thank you.
ありがとう｡
ああ｡
Sure.
会えてよかった バン｡
I'm glad I got to see you, Ban.
またな エレイン｡
I'll see you later, Elaine.
(ｴﾚｲﾝ)ありがとう 兄さん｡
バンを守ってくれて｡
Thank you, Brother.
For protecting Ban.
エレイン！
Elaine!
Looks like we've returned to the real world.
元の世界に戻ったようだな｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)ああ～ びっくりしたぁ｡
Ah, I was so worried.
あっ！ あれは…｡
That's—!
なるほどなぁ｡
自分を仮死状態にして➡
I see... She came to the Capital of the Dead by leaving herself half-dead.
死者の都に来たわけか｡
That means she could wake up at any moment, right?
つぅことは ぼちぼち
目を覚ますんじゃね!?
皆さん 早く逃げましょう！
Everyone, let's hurry and run!
Let's just kill her now.
殺そうぜ 今のうち｡
野蛮だな｡ 石化させる｡
How savage. I'll just petrify her.
No, leave her to me!
うんにゃ！ ここは 俺に任せろ｡
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)
目覚めよ… 目覚めよ 我が弟子よ｡
Wake up.
Wake up, my disciple.
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)あっ これは… ヘルブラム卿｡
You're—!
Lord Helbram!
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)失態だな ギーラよ｡➡
Looks like you failed, Guila.
Perhaps it was too soon for you to face the Seven Deadly Sins—
やはり
七つの大罪の相手には 早すぎ…➡
ん？ お前 その顔は…｡
What happened to your face?
Well, I guess...
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)
いや でも… うん 悪くはないな｡
Yeah...
It's not so bad.
Eh? Eh?!
はい 団長！
ご飯が出来ましたよ～｡ あ～ん！
Here, Captain!
The food is ready!
Open wide!
無理だっつぅの｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)あ～ん！
That's impossible.
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)ねえ ディアンヌ
本当に ケガは もういいの？
Hey, Diane, are you really okay now?
Huh? Oh... Y-Yeah!
えっ!? うっ うん… もう平気｡
Idiot! I bet she was just fakin' it to get attention from Cap'n.
バ～カ！ 団ちょに構ってほしくて
わざと やられたふりしたんだろ｡
ディアンヌは そんな子じゃない！
ギクッ…｡
Diane wouldn't do something like that!
Calm down, you two.
まあ 二人とも落ち着けよ｡
That's right, I forgot to ask earlier.
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)
そういえば聞いてなかった｡➡
この子は
団長と どんな関係なの？
What's your relationship with the Captain?
We're lovers?
愛人的な？
違います！
No!
タッチしたり されたり的な？
メリオダス様!?
We like getting touchy-feely?
Lord Meliodas, please...
あの… ちょっ…｡
She's the kingdom's princess.
王国の王女様だ｡
第三王女だっけ？
あっ はい｡
The third princess, right?
Yes...
お… 王女様!?➡
P-Princess?!
You should've told me sooner!
それを早く言ってよ！
そうと分かれば➡
Had I known, I would've presented myself better!
きちんと正装して… んっ！➡
んん～…｡
いえ あの…｡
No, that's...
Whoa, his clothes changed!
おっ 服が変わった！
そこじゃねぇ！
That's not the point!
You see...
いや～ この姿になるのは
気を張る必要があってさ｡
Maintaing this appearance actually requires a lot of concentration.
豚だな｡
えっ？
He's a pig.
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)七つの大罪
怠惰の罪のキングです｡➡
I am the Grizzly's Sin of Sloth,
King, of the Seven Deadly Sins.
以後 お見知りおきを｡
は… はい こちらこそ｡
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
A-Ah, yes... Likewise.
王女様とは知らず
死者の都での非礼➡
Please forgive my impropriety
back at the Capital of the Dead!
お許しください！
そ… そんなこと…｡
Y-You don't have to...
Please, you can relax.
There's no need for you to be so tense.
あの…
それより そんな緊張しないで➡
もっと 肩の力を抜いてください｡
I... I see... In that case...
はっ はあ… そういうことなら…｡
ふぅ～ 久々で肩凝った｡
Phew, it's been a while. My shoulders are stiff.
Ah, his clothes are back.
あっ 服が戻った｡
だから そこかよ！
You're still stuck on that?
But, Lord King, you really are powerful.
それにしても キング様って
とっても お強いんですね｡
You singlehandedly defeated an enemy
that three people were having trouble with.
メリオダス様たちが
苦戦していた相手を➡
たった一人で圧倒するなんて｡
確かに おいらは強いけどね｡
でも あの聖騎士なら➡
It's true that I am strong, but...
If you guys had used your true strength against that Holy Knight, it should've been a breeze.
君たちが 本来の力を発揮できれば
倒せたはずだよ｡
三人とも 神器はどうしたの？
You three... What happened to your Sacred Treasures?
I lost it.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)なくしちゃった｡
売っちゃった｡
I sold it.
It got stolen.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)盗られちゃった｡
ふがっ！ ありえない！
That's impossible!
Northern Liones - Vannoh District
(族長)
野郎ども！ このまま南下して➡
Bastards!
We'll continue marching south and devour everything in Britannia!
ブリタニアをねぶり
食らい尽くすぞ～！
バリバリバリッ！
(一同)うわぁ～！
Wh-Who are they?
な… なんだ？ こいつら｡
Chief! Those two are Holy Knights!
(蛮族)
族長！ この二人は… 聖騎士だ！
たかが二人で
乗り込んでくるとは…｡
Just two people coming up against us?
面白～い！ 血祭りに挙げてやれ！
How amusing!
We'll throw you guys a bloodbath party!
We love parties! Don't we, Gil?
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)祭りは嫌いじゃねぇぜ｡
なあ ギル？
No. I hate parties.
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)いや 俺は嫌いだ｡
バリバリバリッ！
(一同)うわぁ～！
つれないねぇ｡
じゃあ とっとと終わらせるか！
What a drag...
Guess I'll just end this quickly.
ドゴォーン！
(一同)うわぁ～！
ぎゃあ～～…｡
Although the captured king had the power to foresee the Holy War that would soon be upon us,
(ﾄﾞﾚﾌｧｽ)王は 聖戦を
予知する能力を持ちながら➡
戦を回避するために
我らに剣を置けと命じられた｡➡
he ordered us to lay down our swords in an attempt to avoid the conflict.
だが それは間違いだ｡➡
But that was a mistake!
We, the Holy Knights, are the swords that protect the Liones Kingdom!
我ら聖騎士こそ
リオネスを守る剣！➡
皆 聖戦に備えよ！ 剣を研げ！➡
Everyone, prepare yourselves for war!
I promise you,
約束しよう｡
我ら二大聖騎士長が➡
we, the new Great Holy Knights,
リオネスを
聖戦の勝利に導かんことを！
will lead the Liones Kingdom to victory in this Holy War!
That's quite the flashy speech, Dreyfus.
(ﾍﾝﾄﾞﾘｸｾﾝ)
大層な演説だ ドレファス｡
Let it be, Hendriksen.
そう言うな ヘンドリクセン｡
(衛兵)聖騎士長様｡
ギルサンダー様とハウザー様が➡
Great Holy Knights,
Lord Gilthunder and Lord Hauser have
returned from their fight with the barbarians.
蛮族の討伐から戻られました｡
(ﾄﾞﾚﾌｧｽ)うむ 私の部屋に｡➡
Bring them to my chamber.
Gilthunder, Hauser, good work.
ご苦労だったな
ハウザー ギルサンダー｡
ドレファス聖騎士長
聖戦は いつ起こるんですか？
Great Holy Knight Drefyus,
when exactly is the battle going to begin?
こんなお使いばかりじゃ
体がなまってしょうがない｡
All these little errands are just tiresome.
さあな｡
Who knows?
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)いいかげん
分からないんですか？➡
Isn't that a bit irresponsible?
At least tell us who we're fighting.
せめて 相手ぐらい｡
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)口が過ぎるぞ ハウザー｡
Hauser, you're out of line.
No, it's fine.
(ﾄﾞﾚﾌｧｽ)まあいい｡
それで 七つの大罪だが…｡
Anyway, about the Seven Deadly Sins...
Yes.
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)
はっ｡ キングが 王国を裏切り➡
With King's betrayal,
four of the Sins are now united.
これで
四人が結集したことになります｡
Hey, what's the meaning of this?
おい なんだよ？
まさか 聖戦の相手が➡
Do you mean to tell me that the Holy War is against the Seven Deadly Sins?
七つの大罪だっていうんじゃ
ないだろうな？
That's something I can't confirm yet.
それは まだ なんとも言えない｡
However, there is one thing I can say for sure.
だが
はっきりと言えることが一つある｡
The Seven Deadly Sins, especially
the Dragon's Sin of Wrath, Meliodas,
七つの大罪は…
特に 憤怒の罪のメリオダスは➡
必ず倒さねばならん
脅威ということだ｡
are a threat that must be eliminated.
Holy Knight Dreyfus...
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)ドレファス聖騎士長…｡
Do you remember the Kingdom of Danafor,
who used to rival the Liones Kingdom in power?
(ﾄﾞﾚﾌｧｽ)かつて リオネスと並び
強大な勢力を誇った➡
ダナフォール王国を
知っているだろう？
Yeah, the Kingdom that was
destroyed by some great disaster.
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)
ああ～ 大厄災で滅んだとかいう｡
It was completely annihilated...
(ﾄﾞﾚﾌｧｽ)消滅したのだよ｡➡
by the power of Meliodas,
who had lost himself in his wrath.
憤怒に我を忘れた
メリオダスの力によって｡
You can't be serious!
マジかよ!?
まあ 仮に そうだとしても➡
Even if that was true,
王国には 七つの大罪の
数十倍の聖騎士もいますし➡
the Liones's Holy Knights
vastly outnumber the Sins.
We also have these "New Generation"
Holy Knights showing up one after another!
新世代ってやつも
続々 誕生してるじゃないっすか｡
ポジティブすぎるんだよ お前は｡
You're too much of an optimist.
You're just way too negative.
お前が ネガティブなの｡
Well, I've got some work to do,
so I have to get going.
じゃあ
俺は野暮用もあるんで これで｡
"New Generation," huh?
新世代か…｡
≫ガチャ バタン(ﾄﾞｱの開閉音)
I've received reports of Hendriksen's men calling for several apprentices.
ヘンドリクセン派の者が
数名の聖騎士見習いを➡
呼び出しているとの報告が｡
うむ｡
"New Generation?" What the heck is that?
新世代？ なんだそりゃ？
Holy Knight apprentices who were considered failures
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)
聖騎士になれない見習いの中に➡
ひと晩で突然 聖騎士のような力を
手に入れる者が現れたらしくてさ｡
are suddenly obtaining powers far greater than those of the average Holy Knight.
例えば ギーラ｡➡
Take Guila for example.
If I told you that just a few days ago,
she was an apprentice with barely any power,
彼女は つい先日まで
聖騎士見習いだった…➡
would you believe me?
と言ったら 信じられるかい？
あいつが？
Her?!
Now with all this going on,
そんな状況なのに
七つの大罪結成時に➡
the Sacred Treasures entrusted to us by the King of Liones
リオネス国王から賜った神器を➡
when we formed the Seven Deadly Sins were...
Sold?!
売った!?
店の資金がかかっちゃって｡
I needed money for the bar.
Stolen?!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)盗まれた!?
投獄されたときにな～｡
From when I was locked up.
んん…｡
うぅ… 僕ってば ダメな子？
Am I a bad girl?
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)な… なくしちゃったものは
しょうがないよ｡ うん！
No, not at all! Everyone
misplaces things from time to time.
Come on now, King. No need to
get so fussy over a weapon or two.
まあ
そう鼻息荒げるなよ キングちゃん｡
こいつら
素手でも 結構いけるぜ？
Even without them, they're pretty strong.
Li'l Piggy...
豚君｡
ぶ… 豚君？
L-Li'l Piggy?
例えば この湖を 七つの大罪の
誰かの魔力としよう｡➡
For example,
let's say that this lake represents the power of one of the Sins.
君は この湖の水を
手のひらで どのくらいすくえる？
How much water would you be able to scoop with just your palm?
ひら？
そう｡
Palm?
Right. No matter how much power you have,
どれほどの魔力があろうと
素手では限界がある｡
there's a limit to everything.
But if you use a weapon, such as a Sacred Treasure,
でも 武器を使えば…
それも 神器ともなれば➡
今とは比較にならない魔力を
引き出せる｡
you'd be able to draw incomparably more power than before.
Sacred Treasures are amazing, aren't they?
すげぇだろ 神器って｡
なるほど～！
Ah, I see!
You idiots! How could you get rid of something so valuable!
って お前ら なんで 手放した～!?
はっはっはっはっ｡
どっちにしろ これからは
神器捜しも必要になるよ｡
Either way, we have to search
for your Sacred Treasures now.
That is, if we're serious about saving the Kingdom.
王国を 本気で救うつもりならね｡
あの…｡
ん？
Um...
Lord King, you've been inside
the city recently, haven't you?
キング様は 城内の者と一緒に➡
行動していたのですよね？
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)うん まあね｡
Yeah, I guess.
My father and sister...
父上や姉様 国王や ほかの王女が
どうしているか知りませんか？
The other princesses...
Do you know if they're okay?
いや ごめん… 残念だけど｡
I don't, unfortunately. Sorry.
I... see...
そう… ですか｡
Why is this my room?!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)
なぜ おいらが この部屋なんだ!?
There are no other rooms.
ほかに空き部屋はない！
じゃあ おいらは 外で野宿するよ｡
そうすれば ディアンヌとも…｡
Fine. I'll just sleep outside like a bum.
I'll get to be with Diane, anywa—
Come on, Master Hawk. Let's get some shuteye!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ホーク師匠 寝よ～ぜ｡
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)やめろ！➡
You reek of alcohol! Let go of me!
酒臭い！ 放せ！
身代わり作戦成功｡ ふっふっ！
Scapegoat strategy, success!
≫コンコン(ﾉｯｸ)
あっ｡
That's really pretty.
きれいだよな それ｡
はい｡
Thank you.
My older sister Margaret gave me this earring for my fifteenth birthday.
このイヤリングは
私の１５の誕生日に➡
マーガレット姉様が
くれたものなんです｡
She was very kind and gentle.
とても穏やかで 優しい｡
ふ～ん｡
The second princess, Veronica, was tomboyish,
第二王女のベロニカ姉様は
おてんばで➡
男勝りに 剣を振り回しては
父上に叱られていて｡
and would get in trouble with our
father for swordplay with the boys.
We used to play with Gilthunder a lot.
ギルサンダーも
よく遊んでくれて…｡
It was fun back then...
楽しかったな｡
心配すんな｡
Don't worry!
お前の姉さんも おやじさんも
みんな助け出す｡
We'll save your father and sisters, along with everyone else!
そのためにも旅してるんだぜ｡
That's why we're on this journey!
メリオダス様…｡
だから➡
Lord Meliodas...
So...
今日は もう寝ろよ｡ さっ おいで｡
You should get some rest for tonight.
Come on, sleep over here!
You never learn, do you?
お前 ほんとに懲りないな！
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)んんっ！
(ﾂｲｰｺﾞ)んごっ… あっ 貴様！➡
You wench, what are you doing here?
なぜ ここに!?
あなたに答える義理はありません｡
I have no obligation to tell you.
Confirmed! I'm gonna kill you later!
決定！ あとでシメてやるわ｡
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)ヘンドリクセン聖騎士長と
話をするのではなかったのですか？
Weren't we summoned by the Great
Holy Knight Hendriksen? Where is he?
≫(ﾍﾝﾄﾞﾘｸｾﾝ)私なら ここだよ｡
(２人)あっ｡
I'm right here.
確か ツイーゴ君とジェリコ君…
だったかね？
If I recall correctly,
you're Twigo and Jericho, correct?
Wh-What...
なんだ!?
これは！
is this?!
Welcome, ye warriors who thirst for new powers!
ようこそ
新しき力を渇望する勇士たちよ｡
Today, you two shall be reborn.
(ﾍﾝﾄﾞﾘｸｾﾝ)お前たちは
今日 ここで生まれ変わる｡
飲め｡ 魔神族の血だ｡
Drink it.
This is demon's blood.
あの山の斜面に
へばりついているのが➡
That town at the base of the mountainside is Byzel.
バイゼル｡ 商人の町だ｡
It's a merchant town.
Is it really here?
本当にあるのか？
こないだの客が➡
The other day
誰にも扱えないような
大きなハンマーが➡
we heard a customer say a huge hammer that
no one could use was brought here, didn't we?
運び込まれたって
言ってただろ｡
That no one can use?
誰にも扱えない？
まさか ディアンヌの…｡
It can't be. Diane's?!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)それよか
俺の服を なんとかしてくれよぉ｡
Who cares about that? Can someone
do something about my clothes first?
Just go shirtless with an apron or something.
裸にエプロンでも着けてろよ｡
Who cares about that?!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)そんなことより～‼
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ ﾎｰｸ)うわ～！
なんで 僕だけ留守番なの～？
Why am I house-sitting again?!
しかたないだろ｡ 何年か前に➡
It's not your fault.
Some giants caused an uproar at a festival a few years back, so they're banned now.
巨人族が 祭りで暴れて以来➡
出入り禁止らしいんだよ｡
確かめたら すぐ戻ってくるって｡
We'll be back once we've confirmed the rumor.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)嫌だ！ つまんな～い！
No! It's so boring!
あの… 私が残ります｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)えっ いいの？
Um... I'll stay back as well.
Huh, really?
I want to have some girl talk every once in a while!
たまには 女の子同士
おしゃべりしたいもの｡
Girl talk?
女の子同士？ うふふっ！
All right. Well, let's go!
よし じゃあ行くか！
Hot off the anvil! Great swords from a skillful blacksmith!
(商人)買った 買った～！
腕のいい鍛冶の剣だ！
This is from a royal tomb and has a fascinating history!
王家の墓に眠っていた
いわく付きの品だよ！
How are we gonna find anything like this, Cap'n?
(ﾊﾞﾝ)この中 捜す気かよ 団ちょ｡
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)本当に 裸エプロン｡
You really went shirtless with an apron...
武器屋でも当たってみるか｡
Let's check out the weapon shops first.
≪(ｹｲﾝ)何かお捜しかね？
ん？
Are you looking for something?
(ｹｲﾝ)ひっく…
それとも 祭りの参加者かの？
Or are you participants in the festival?
No, we're searching for a weapon.
いや 武器を捜してるんだよ｡
大きなハンマー｡
ここにあるって聞いたんだけど｡
A big hammer. We heard it was somewhere around here, but...
Ah, now that's easy to find.
ああ～ それなら簡単｡➡
ほれ あの裏じゃ｡
Over there, behind that thing.
That's Diane's Sacred Treasure! "Gideon!"
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)
これは ディアンヌのギデオン！
ほんとにあったな｡
It really was here!
Okay! The annual Byzel Fight Festival is about to begin!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)さあ
年に一度のバイゼル喧嘩祭りが➡
始まるぜ～！
(一同)わあ～！
武器の使用は 一切不可｡
The use of weapons is completely prohibited!
拳と拳で語り合いたい野郎どもは
すぐエントリー！
If any of you bastards want to let
your fists do the talking, step right up!
優勝者には 金貨１００枚と➡
The grand prize is a hundred gold coins! Also, you'll get a giant's war hammer!
副賞として
この巨人の戦鎚もプレゼントだ！
Such a barbaric festival...
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)
野蛮な祭りだな｡ ねえ 団長…｡
Right, Captain—
We're totally entering, right, Cap'n?
当然 エントリーだな｡
白黒つけるか｡
ふがっ！➡
Shall we put an end to this once and for all, Ban?
えっ？
お～い 出場するぞ！
Hey, three fighters here!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)おいらは やだよ！
ん？ おっ｡
I don't want to!
This isn't some kiddie game at a carnival!
(ﾀｲｽﾞｰ)
これは ガキの祭りじゃねぇんだ｡➡
引っ込んでな！
話が よく見えねぇんだけど｡
Get outta here!
I don't really get what you're trying to say.
Hey, geezer...
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)おっさん➡
野暮なこと言うなよ｡ 祭りだろ？
No need to be so barbaric. It's a festival, right?
(ﾀｲｽﾞｰ)うっ… てめぇ！ ちっ！
You bastard.
俺が ３年連続優勝の
タイズーと知っての行動だろうな？
You know that I'm the three-time champion Taizoo, don't you?
All right!
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)さてね｡ 何しろ
毎年 仕事に邪魔され続けで…｡
Every year, I've wanted to enter,
but my job kept getting in the way.
Finally, it's my long-awaited Fight Festival debut!
いや～！
やっと 念願の初参加だぜ！
So let's all just have some fun!
まっ 楽しくやろうぜ｡ へへっ！
I've definitely seem him somewhere before...
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)どっかで見たような…｡
And now the Fight Festival preliminaries shall begin!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)では これより
喧嘩祭り予選を始める｡➡
参加者は 闘技舞台へ！
All participants, come to the fighting ring!
あの若造…｡
よっと｡
That brat...
All right!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)ディアンヌと
留守番してたかったな｡
I just wanted to house-sit with Diane...
As I expected, you've finally shown yourselves, Seven Deadly Sins.
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)
やはり現れたね 七つの大罪｡
Griamor.
グリアモール｡
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)御意｡
Understood.
Well, let's go get Diane's Sacred Treasure back!
さて じゃあ ディアンヌの神器を
取り戻すとするか！
We're going back and forth on a dead-end street, yo
ittari kitari de ikidomari yo
This abandoned dream is a bitter experience, yo
mihatenu yume wa kori gori kori gori yo
After all, this world we live in is transient, yo
shosen konoyo wa ukiyo no sekai
Open up and defy them all to find high spirits, yo
hirakinaoreba NORINORINORINORI yo
High spirits, yo!
NORINORI yo
Throw in the firewood to reignite
maki wo kubero tayasu na sono hi wo
Your blazing passion before it goes out
tsuki ugokasu MONO wa sou kandou sa
The future will be fine as long as it shines brightly
mirai wa tada kagayaite kurete ireba ii’nda
We switched our intense rampage on
bokura wa Gan Gan abare MO-DO
Making seven sounds of thunder
todorokasu Boom Boom nanatsu no oto
Heading toward an ever-bright tomorrow
Rin Rin hikaru ashita e to susumou
We're ready to shoot the place up
bokura wa Bang Bang HAJI ke MO-DO
Jumping here and there as we go
buttobasu Ran Dom SUTAIRU de ikou yo
Shining through like a diamond
Bling Bling hikaru DAIYAMONDO
Let's go, now we can fly high
iku ze Now we can fly high
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)魔神族の血？
Demon's... blood?
The Demon Clan should've been sealed
away for eternity by the Holy Maiden Clan
古の大戦で女神族に敗れ➡
永劫に封印されたはずの存在が➡
after losing to them in the Ancient War.
なぜ 妖精の森で発見されたか
見当はつかぬ｡➡
Why it was found in the Fairy
King's Forest, we have no idea.
However, if you drink this,
and you're compatible with it...
ただ
これを飲み もし適応できれば➡
自制の下に 魔力を 飛躍的に
引き上げることが可能だ｡➡
You'll gain much more power... assuming you can control it.
ギーラのように｡
(２人)あっ｡
Like Guila has.
You wish for power, don't you?
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)力が欲しいのだろう？
力…｡
Power?
Power!
力！
うわぁ～～！
(ﾂｲｰｺﾞ)ぐわぁ～～！
うっ うっ… ぐはっ！
うぅ～…｡
Only one of you is compatible.
適応は １人か｡
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)そのようですな｡
Seems like it.
なんだ？
この かつてない感覚は…｡
What is this new feeling?
け… 決定！ わしは今
爆発的な力を 手に入れ…➡
C-Confirmed! I have attained the power to explode!
ぐわっ！
わし… 爆発… けってぇ…｡
Confirmed! I'm about to explode—
バーン！
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)うっ… ごほっ ごほっ！➡
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)ようこそ こちら側へ｡
Welcome.
Now you're on our side, Jericho.
Next Episode's Report
The Seven Deadly Sins' Fox's Sin of Greed, Ban, is immortal.
＜七つの大罪 強欲の罪
強欲の罪のバンは 不死身である＞
＜ たとえ こうなろうと…＞
ぐわぁ～！
Even if this happens.
＜ こうなろうと＞
ううっ！
Or this happens!
＜ こうなろうと！＞
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ぶぎぃ～…｡
Or even if this happens!
＜決して死ぬことはない｡
必ず 無傷でよみがえるのだ＞
He will never die. He will definitely return completely unharmed.
じゃあよ
こうなったら どうなんの？
Well, what happens in this situation?
(ﾊﾞﾝ)次回 『七つの大罪』
｢バイゼル喧嘩祭り｣｡➡
Next time, on The Seven Deadly Sins: "Byzel Fight Festival."
みんな
ケガには気をつけようぜ～｡
Everyone, be careful you don't get hurt too badly.
Episode 10
Byzel Fight Festival
鹿児島県･種子島宇宙センターから
の打ち上げが
明日に延期されていた小惑星探査
機｢はやぶさ２｣だが､